

123 Pine Brook Dr, Miami, FL 12345 jessica la ng @ example.com (12 3) 456-7 890 An Optometrist with eight years of professional experience specializing in patient education, communication, patient relations, and refractive services. A strong history of delivering compassionate and empathetic care to patients suffering from a wide range of health issues.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

OPTOMETRIST

Better Eye Care, Miami, FL I May 2016 - Present

- Build relationships with a diverse range of patients, conduct eye exams, and prescribe eyeglasses and contact Lenses based on refractive errors and ocular diseases
- Educate patients on diagnosis,treatment plans, pre-op instructions, and post operative-care to drive positive patient outcomes following surgical procedures
- Communicate diagnosis, eye diseases, and degenerative disorders with empathy and compassion and provide quality care services to improve quality of life

OPTOMETRIST

The Vision Center, Miami, FL I May 2014 - May 2016

- Performed eye exams, provided vision therapy, and identified optimal eye care solutions for patients based on age,
 diagnosis, and long-term health needs
- Treated patients suffering from a wide range of refractive errors and eye diseases, including glaucoma, cataracts, diabetes, and macular degeneration

EDUCATION

DOCTOR OF OPTOMETRY

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.S.) BIOLOGY University of Miami, Miami, FL | September 2010 - May 2014

University of Miami, Miami, FL I September 2006 - May 2010

KEY SKILLS

- Patient Education
- Optometry Services
- ◆ Communication
- ♦ Patient Relations
- Quality Care

CERTIFICATIONS

 Licensed Optometrist, State of Florida, License #1234567